

### CONTACT ME AT



in @eyupbatuhansevinc

#### MY PORTFOLIO

www.batuhansevinc.me

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• Project Management

•••• Software Development

•••• Unity

•••• C#

•••• Java

●●●● Process Improvement

#### LANGUAGES

Turkish (Native)

English (C1)

German (A2)

## **BATUHAN SEVINC**

#### UNITY DEVELOPER & SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

Sofware engineering student in senior class at Izmir University of Economics. Freelance Junior Game Developer & Software Engineer with 2 plus years of experience. Currently working as a freelance Junior & Mid Unity & Software Developer.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Unity Game Developer

Unicode Games, Izmir-Turkey

2020 - Present

- Contribute ideas in a collaborative, supportive team environment.
- Suggest improvements to the developed product.
- Fix bugs during development and in production.
- Analyze code and present technical options.
- · Help to scope, estimate and coordinate sprint tasks and work with crossfunctional team including product QA, design and art.
- Work closely with engineering leadership to architect, build, refactor and maintain mobile(Android) client/server tech and features that can scale to millions of users.
- Developing Hyper-Casual games using with Unity Game Engine.

# Freelance Game Developer (Unity)

Self-Employed, Izmir-Turkey

2019 - 2020

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Collaborated with other designers
- Translated requirements into polished, high-level designs

### Front Desk Associate & Computer Technician (Summer Work & Travel Program 2020)

Brett-Robinson Vacation Rentals, Alabama-USA

2019 - 2020

• Summer Work & Travel Program job.

Waiter (Summer Work & Travel Program 2019)

Zephyr Cove Resort, Nevada-USA

2018 - 2019

• Summer Work & Travel Program job.

Busser (Summer Work & Travel Program 2018)

Zephyr Cove Resort, Nevada-USA

2017 - 2018

• Summer Work & Travel Program job.

## EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

# BSc in Software Engineering

Izmir University of Economics

2016 - present

- Coordinate designs and implementation with QA to enable automated and manual testing.
- Write unit tests for components.
- Design and implement gaming software platforms(UNITY, UNREAL ENGINE) for mobile, embeded and desktop platforms.
- Senior Project: GNAW-> Genetic Algorithm Wizard, Python based algorithm and problem wizard working with genetic algorithms.

### AS in Computer Programming

Izmir University of Economics

2014 - 2016

- Database systems Mysql,Microsoft Access.
- PHP, HTML, .NET, CSS development.
- JAVA,C# Programming and project development.
- Android Studio, Visual Studio, VS Code supported courses and developing project applications.
- Mobile Game development courses.
- Awards: Honour Student certificate in 2014-2015 fall semester.